Guide to the Robert L. Bracklow Photograph Collection 1882-1918 (bulk, 1896-1905) PR 8
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Alland Purchase, 1
  - Subseries I.1: Alland Purchase: Negatives, 2
    - Robert L. Bracklow's stationery store, 18 Maiden Lane [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1830)
    - Island, steamers, docks, etc. [] (Item 1831)
    - Men and boys bathing under boat house or pier [] (Item 1831)
    - Summer estate on island or promontory [] (Item 1832)
    - M. Colford? Country inn or club [] (Item 1833)
    - Snow covered tree and clothes lines in city back yard [] (Item 1834)
    - Tree grown lot on New York city street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1835)
    - View up bank to castellated house [] (Item 1836)
    - Seascape with three masted sailboats [] (Item 1837)
    - Suburban house [] (Item 1838)
    - Shore Hotel, J. E. Hoogland [] (Item 1839)
    - Seascape with single masted sailboats [] (Item 1840)
    - Wooded drives leading to three story house [] (Item 1841)
    - Harbor view of N.Y.C. skyline dominated by Singer Tower [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1842)
    - McDougal Alley [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1843)
    - Early stone house with iron portico on all sides [] (Item 1844)
    - Stone church with tower in the suburbs [] (Item 1845)
    - Steamer Priscilla [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 1846)
    - N.Y. Camera Club exhibit [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1894 (Item 1847)
    - N.Y. Camera Club exhibit, another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1894 (Item 1847)
    - W. M. Briggs [] (Item 1848)
    - Portrait of Robert Bracklow probably taken by W.M. Briggs [], 1904 (Item 1848)
    - Dewey Arch. Good study of cabs and carriages on Fifth Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1849)
    - Dewey Arch, another view from opposite direction. Street cleaner & cyclists in foreground [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1849)
    - Dewey Arch, close up with cab and crowd [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1849)
    - Dewey Arch, close up from other direction with crowd [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 1849)
    - N.Y. Camera Club exhibit, 1894 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1850)
    - N.Y. Camera Club exhibit, 1894, another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1850)
    - N.Y. Camera Club exhibit, 1894, another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1850)
    - Grant's Tomb [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1851)
    - Photographer's tent, 106th St. & Boulevard [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1852)
    - T. P. W. Perkins blacksmith shop with old house beyond [] (Item 1853)
    - Church [] (Item 1854)
    - Ascension Memorial Church Protestant Episcopal, built 1862, 243 W. 43rd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1855)
    - Bloomingdale Methodist Episcopal Church, built 1850, 43rd St. between Seventh and Eighth Aves. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1855)
    - United Presbyterian Church, 44th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1856)
    - Holy Cross Lyceum, 321 West 43rd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 1857)
    - Governor's Island with steamer Mount Desert in foreground [New York (N.Y.)] (Item 1857)
    - Episcopal Church [183rd St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1902 (Item 1858)
    - Boundbrook battle monument, Boundbrook, N. J. [Boundbrook (N.J.)] (Item 1858)
    - Custom House statue at left front [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1859)
    - Custom House statue at right of building [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1859)
    - Custom House statue at left of steps [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1859)
    - Last photograph of R. L. Bracklow, 7/17/18. Good studio portrait [], [1918] (Item 1859)
    - St. Marks Church, 2nd Ave. and 10th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1900 (Item 1860)
    - R. G. Hutchinson, Stationer and Printer. 84 William St. Young R. L. Bracklow was employed by Hutchinson and later bought the business. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1897 (Item 1861)
    - "Sic transit gloria." Ruin of old country mansion and new city church just beyond. Oct.26, 1890? [] (Item 1862)
    - Chatham National Bank entrance, 192 Broadway [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1863)
    - Marine view [] (Item 1864)
    - Pilgrim statue in Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1865)
    - Interior showing family portraits on wall [Parents of R.L. Bracklow?] [] (Item 1866)
    - Another interior in same early house [] (Item 1867)
    - Century Restaurant, next door to Barnum & Co. envelope mfgr. [William Street] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1868)
    - Western National Bank front close up, 13 Nassau St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 1869)
    - Sailors' church with fish weathervane [] (Item 1870)
    - Another interior similar to 1866 [] (Item 1871)
    - Another similar interior, probably in Bracklow's house [] (Item 1871)
    - [Flatiron Building] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2000)
    - Columbus Statue, the Mall, Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2001)
    - [Whitehall building] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2002)
    - [Whitehall building] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2003)
    - [Appellate Division, Courthouse, 25th St. & Madison Square] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2004)
    - [Hotel Albemarle and Hoffman House] Broadway, Fifth Ave. and 24th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2005)
    - [Robert Bracklow in Camera Club darkroom] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2007)
    - [Pres.? Church] 22nd St. & 4th Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2008)
    - [Dewey Arch, 1898] [side view] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2009)
    - [Giuseppi Verdi statue] Verdi Square, Broadway, Amsterdam Ave., 73rd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2010)
    - Columbus Statue, the Mall, Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2011)
    - Bust of Beethoven in park [] (Item 2012)
    - [Fireman's monument], Greenwich Village [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1893 (Item 2013)
    - [Dewey Arch, Fifth Avenue] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2014)
    - [Orcutt's Restaurant, 141 Fulton, just before removal to 102 Fulton St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2015)
    - [Old New York house] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 2016)
    - [Fowle & Johnston. Gen. Wolfe Tavern, 1762-1892] [Medford (Mass.)] (Item 2017)
    - Rear of 230 William St. from 5th floor of Sugar House [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 2018)
    - Washington Bridge with Highbridge in distance [Washington Bridge (N.Y.)] (Item 2019)
    - [Dewey Arch, Fifth Ave.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 2020)
      This image also appears in Album 6, page 4
    - Boulevard Mission of the Reformed Presbyterian Church [in old Greek revival mansion] [], 1890 (Item 2021)
    - [House interior looking through portiers to bedroom] [], 1892 (Item 2022)
    - Abbey Theatre, Casino Theater and Hotel Normandy, 39th and Broadway [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 2023)
    - Union League Club, 5th Ave. & 30th St., decorated for McKinley & Hobart [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2024)
    - Sugar House, (Rhinelander) with building in front removed. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 2025)
    - Century Association & N.Y. Academy of Medicine, 109 E. 15th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2026)
    - Monument to captors of Andre, Tarrytown, N.Y. [Tarrytown (N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 2027)
    - Washington Arch, 5th Ave. & Washington Square, April 7, 1895 [before bas-reliefs were added] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2028)
    - [Demolition of theatre] [] (Item 2029)
    - Ogden Goelet Mansion, Broadway & 19th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1893 (Item 2030)
    - Old London Streets [N.Y. City] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1893 (Item 2031)
    - Dewey Arch, 1898 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2032)
    - General Theological Seminary, Ninth Ave. between 20th and 21st Sts [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 2033)
    - Corner Nassau & Liberty Sts. [Anton Sondheim & Son] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1894 (Item 2034)
    - Bank for Savings [previous to removal to S. W. corner of 4th Ave. & 22nd St.], Bleecker St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 2035)
    - Livingston Manor [Livingston Manor (N.Y.)], 1890 (Item 2036)
    - [Top of Dewey Arch] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 2037)
      This image also appears in Album 6, page 2
    - [Verdi statue, different view from 2010] Broadway and Amsterdam Aves. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2038)
    - Grace Reformed Church, Seventh Ave. and 54th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2039)
    - Church of the Ascension, 10th St. & 5th Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2040)
    - 14 Astor Place [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2041)
    - [Croton Reservoir, cor. 5th Ave. & 42nd St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2042)
    - [Church and George Bruce branch, New York Free Circulating Library] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2043)
    - [Anderson Building] Maiden Lane, including #78, Bracklow's shop [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2044)
    - [Corner of Madison Ave. & 28th St. Prince George Hotel & Hotel Latham in distance] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2045)
    - [Corner of Broadway and 25th St., St. James Hotel beyond] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2046)
    - [Statue to Thorvaldsen] [], 1896 (Item 2047)
      This image also appears in Album 16, page 18
    - [Interior of National Bank of Commerce] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2048)
    - [End view of Dewey Arch] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 2049)
      This image also appears in Album 6, page 1
    - Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show performers' tents [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2050)
    - Interior of school classroom, 1892 [] (Item 2051)
    - Columbus Arch from S. W. side of Fifth Ave., Oct.21, 1892 [before sculptured group was added on top] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2052)
    - Columbus Arch, during parade, Oct.12, 1892 [with sculptured group on top] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2053)
    - Dewey Arch [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2054)
    - [Corner of E. 19th St. Old house on corner, Herts Brothers bldg. beyond] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2055)
    - [2 bldgs. About to be demolished, including former home of Hazard Mfg. Co., removed to 50 Dey St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2056)
    - [Fort Totten?] [Queens (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2057)
    - [S. W. across Bryant Park, from 42nd Street] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2058)
    - [The Bank for Savings, S. W. corner 4th Ave. & 22nd St.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2059)
    - Hotel Manhattan [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2060)
    - [F. & M. Schaefer Brewing Co.] Park Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2061)
    - [Presbyterian Church? 42nd St. between 5th & 6th Ave.] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2062)
    - [Western National Bank], Nassau St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2063)
    - [4th Presby. Church], 91st St. & West End Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2064)
    - [2 old Greek revival houses] [] (Item 2065)
    - [New York Free Circulating Library, like No. 2043] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2066)
    - [Bust of Washington Irving in a park] [] (Item 2067)
    - Church of St. Mary the Virgin [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 2068)
    - [4th Presby. Church], 91st St. & West End Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2069)
    - Rhinelander Sugar House, Rose St., 1892 before removal of building in front [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2070)
    - Rockingham, early apartment house [], 1892 (Item 2071)
    - Columbian Celebration, Oct.12, 1892, looking down on parade from roof of 930 Broadway [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2072)
    - Casino, Abbey's Theatre and Telephone Bldg., 38th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 2073)
    - New York from West Hoboken, N. J. [West Hoboken (N.J.)], 1891 (Item 2074)
    - 42nd St. & 7th Ave. (Overin's Stables, 600-610) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1889 (Item 2075)
    - London Terrace, 23rd St. between Eighth and Ninth Aves. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 2076)
    - Hotel Brevoort, Fifth Ave. and 8th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 2077)
    - Looking down Henry St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 2078)
    - [Central Park view] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2079)
    - New York Public Library, 5 Ave. & 42 St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2080)
    - [John W. Quicy & Co., 88 William St., cor. Platt, Cut nails, iron, & c., c. a. 1896] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2081)
    - [Old New York House. Same Subject as No. 2016] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2082)
    - [Madison Square Garden] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1899 (Item 2083)
      This image also appears in Album 6, page 5
    - [Looking down Henry St., new building going up on corner, 1895] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2084)
    - 526 Hudson St. [Barber shop in basement. Also No. 522, 524, 528] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 2085)
    - Broadway Tabernacle from 7th floor of "Alpine" apartment house, 34th St. & Broadway [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 2086)
    - Cottage Place [], 1892 (Item 2087)
    - Columbus Ave. [squatter's shack], 1890 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2088)
    - Morton St. from Hudson St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 2089)
    - Shiff Bldg., Duane St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2090)
    - Shiff Bldg., Duane St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2090)
    - Hudson & Leonard Sts. [New York Mercantile Exchange Bldg. (H. O. Wilbur & Sons)] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2091)
    - [Grace Church and Fleischmann's Vienna Model Bakery, 1893, from Fifth Ave. and 10th Street] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2092)
    - Looking southeast at Grace Church, from Fifth Ave. and 10th Street [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2092)
    - Old houses, Lafayette Place, below 4th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 2093)
    - Columbus Parade, 1892. [From roof of 930 B'way, Oct. 12, 1892. Similar to No. 2072] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2094)
    - Bridge in Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2095)
    - [Old New York house] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2096)
    - All Angels Church, 81st St. and West End [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1890 (Item 2097)
    - Classroom, 1892. [] (Item 2098)
    - All Angels Church, 81st St. and West End [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 2099)
    - Three story city residence [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2100)
    - Suburban stone church with tower [] (Item 2101)
    - Interior of NCB (National City Bank?) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2102)
    - Fifth Avenue Presbyterian Church [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2103)
    - Washington Bridge [Washington Bridge (New York, N.Y.)], 1892 (Item 2104)
    - Colonial house with modern house next to it [] (Item 2105)
    - Brick colonial house [] (Item 2106)
    - Church of St. Mary the Virgin [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 2107)
    - Close up of entrance to Old church of St. Mary the Virgin [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 2107)
    - Church of St. Chrysostom, Seventh Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 2108)
    - Central Bapt. Church (Next door to Geroge Bruch Branch, N.Y. Free Circulating Library) [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2109)
    - Interior of bedroom [] (Item 2110)
    - Inn from Highpoint [], 1895 (Item 2111)
    - Boating scene with sailboats [] (Item 2112)
    - Lighthouse [] (Item 2113)
    - Lighthouse and house [] (Item 2113)
    - Loking east from Highpoint [], 1895 (Item 2114)
    - St. Bartholomew Church, corner Madison Ave.& 44th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2115)
    - Holy Trinity Church, 42nd St. & Madison Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2116)
    - Marble Collegiate Church, Fifth Ave. & 29th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2117)
    - Church [] (Item 2118)
    - Meeting house of the First Presbyterian Society Erected 1756. Close up. [] (Item 2119)
    - Three tepees of Buffalo Bill Show [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2120)
    - Ten story business building next to M. N. Packard Co., teas, coffees, spices. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2121)
    - Mansion [] (Item 2122)
    - Goelet Mansion (rear view), Broadway and 19th St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2123)
    - Old fort-house, New Paltz [New Paltz (N.Y.)] (Item 2124)
    - Puritan statue, Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2125)
    - Old house on the side of a hill [] (Item 2126)
    - The inn from Orchard Point [], 1894 (Item 2127)
    - Columbus Statue at Columbus Circle [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2150)
    - Old two story mansion [] (Item 2151)
    - Old two story frame house by lake shore (or ocean) [Fort Hamilton (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 2151)
      This image also appears in Album 1, page 47
    - Interurban trolley car marked "Ferry" and "Bergen County"… [New Jersey] (Item 2152)
    - City street with dray and sandwich man with sign [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2153)
    - City street with hack and dray [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2153)
    - City street, team at watering trough. Labeled "Horse drinking fountain." [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2153)
    - Bathing beach with Balmer's Bathing Pavilion in background [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 2154)
    - Bathing beach with Balmer's Bathing Pavilion in background, another view [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 2154)
    - Waterfront scene at Battery [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2155)
    - Waterfront scene at Battery; another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2155)
    - Harbor view with battle ships [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1898 (Item 2156)
      This image also appears in Album 1, page 48
    - Harbor view with battle ships, different view [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1898 (Item 2156)
    - Harbor view with battle ships, sailboats [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1898 (Item 2156)
    - Evening Post Office with news bulletin boards in front. Luckey & Sammis, Tailors [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 2157)
      This image also appears in Album 28, page 4
    - Evening Post Office with news bulletin boards in front. Another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 2157)
      This image also appears in Album 28, page 3
    - F. W. Dierks café, with spread eagle in metal at corner [] (Item 2158)
    - Webster's statue [] (Item 2159)
    - "Geo. Washington Headquarters Broad St. 1890" [Fraunces Tavern before restoration] [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2160)
    - Stages at South Ferry, 1893 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2161)
    - "Billy [goat] of Bronxdale, 1890" [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2162)
    - Cow grazing at edge of street, New York City, 1893 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2162)
    - Water gate to Hudson at time of Hudson-Fulton Celebration [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2163)
    - View of ? St. from corner of Ninth Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2164)
    - Claremont and Grant's Tomb from river [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2165)
    - Claremont and Grant's Tomb from river [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2165)
    - West Point Military Academy [West Point (N.Y.)] (Item 2166)
    - Battleship in river [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1898 (Item 2167)
      This image also appears in Album 1, page 49
    - Battleship in river, another view [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)], 1898 (Item 2167)
    - Bronze base of flag pole at Public Library, showing buildings across Fifth Ave. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1912 (Item 2168)
    - West 42nd St. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2169)
    - New York Journal Bldg. With Spanish-American War news bulletins [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 2170)
      This image also appears in Album 28, page 10
    - New York Press Bldg. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 2170)
      This image also appears in Album 28, page 7
    - New York Daily News Bldg. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1898 (Item 2170)
      This image also appears in Album 28, page 6
    - Steamship Row at Bowling Green [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2171)
    - Steamship Row at Bowling Green, another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2171)
    - Battery Park Concert Garden [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2172)
    - Battery Park Concert Garden, another view [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2172)
    - Ericcson statue [] (Item 2173)
    - Barge Office at Battery [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2174)
    - Scene at Battery Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2174)
    - Excavations at Battery Park? [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2175)
    - Library, N.Y.U., at Heights (before Hall of Fame) [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2176)
    - Old cottage on knoll, up town N.Y.C. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2177)
    - Sailing ships at piers [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 2178)
    - Sailing ships in harbor [Hudson River (N.Y. and N.J.)] (Item 2178)
    - N.Y.U. up-town campus [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2179)
    - N.Y.U. up-town campus [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2179)
    - Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2180)
    - Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2180)
    - Two teams on canal tow path [] (Item 2181)
    - Two different teams of mules on canal tow path [] (Item 2181)
    - Cyclists on country road [Sudbury (Mass.)], 1898 (Item 2182)
      This image also appears in Album 1, page 42
    - Two women walking on country road [Sudbury (Mass.)], 1898 (Item 2182)
      This image also appears in Album 1, page 40
    - Street scene in downtown N.Y.C. [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2183)
    - Theatre? [] (Item 2184)
    - Riverside Drive park with open freight tracks below at left [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2185)
    - Bronx Park [Bronx (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2186)
    - Plan of N.Y.S. Barge Canal [] (Item 2187)
    - Lock in N.Y.S. Barge Canal [] (Item 2187)
    - Distant view of hospital or church building or college [] (Item 2188)
    - Performer from "Streets of Cairo", Midway, Pan American Exposition, Buffalo [Buffalo (N.Y.)], 1901 (Item 2189)
    - Midway, Pan American Exposition, Buffalo, two other performers in native dress [Buffalo (N.Y.)] (Item 2189)
    - Midway, Pan American Exposition, Buffalo, with native conveyance drawn by dromedaries and camels [Buffalo (N.Y.)] (Item 2190)
    - Temple of Music at Midway, Pan American Exposition, Buffalo [Buffalo (N.Y.)] (Item 2190)
    - Oriental scribe at Midway, Pan American Exposition, Buffalo [Buffalo (N.Y.)] (Item 2190)
    - Elephants performing at Bostock's Wild Animal Show [Buffalo (N.Y.)] (Item 2191)
    - Bostock's Wild Animal Show, elephants doing another trick [Buffalo (N.Y.)] (Item 2191)
    - Bostock's Wild Animal Show, elephants doing another trick [Buffalo (N.Y.)] (Item 2191)
    - Brighton Beach, 1895 [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2192)
    - Brighton Beach [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 2192)
    - Brighton Beach, 1895, another view [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2193)
    - Brighton Beach, another view [Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)], 1895 (Item 2193)
    - Soldiers' and Sailors' Monument fountain, Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2194)
    - Soldiers' and Sailors' Monument fountain, Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2194)
    - Soldiers' and Sailors' Monument fountain, Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2194)
    - Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2195)
    - Central Park [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2195)
    - Metropolitan Opera House [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)], 1890 (Item 2196)
    - Projected N.Y. State [barge?] canal [] (Item 2197)
    - Dredge at work [] (Item 2197)
    - Cohoes Falls? Copy of painting [] (Item 2197)
    - North River & Vesey St., 4/5/1890 [Manhattan (New York, N.Y.)] (Item 2198)